[{"answer": "It's rather difficult for us to think of another planet as a neighbor", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " The present situation", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " I'm afraid that would be a little awkward. It's", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " You know about the that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " I'll tell you, my friend", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " They have cemeteries. But not like this one... You see, they don't have any wars", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Your name my friend", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " I been looking for you all afternoon", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The boss is leaving for that place tomorrow. If I could tell him I was getting married", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "A good insurance salesman wouldn't give you time to think", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Gee, why, Mom? He's my best friend... And he's awful good in arithmetic. He even helps Professor my friend", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Sure we did! He wasn't there but we went to see him. And Mr. my friend showed him how to do his arithmetic", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He's not there.  But look what I found in his roo", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Looks real to me", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I want to know what he told you last night", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Did you believe what he told you?  I have a reason for asking this", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Are you crazy? After what happened today", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Important? Of course it's important. The point is we can do something about it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I feel different right now", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I'm not going to marry anybody", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " It's only a few blocks to my friend's", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend?  But he's a robot. I mean", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Hello", "docId": "Day-the-Earth-Stood-Still_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " I was", "qsentId": 24}]